how goes your search for the Dragon
sorry boss toss lucky old hat I'm not
sure if mama would feel the same
what was that I'm always a critic how
fare you papa
but I know I can trust
is it magic that you do it is not much
but the power of the Spirit
your master is a mysterious looking
fellow your sword is magnificent it is
one of the legendary plays of my family
do you Gigi
only the best ones why do you hide your
face on me without fear or pity the
hammer or the sword the hammer is more
than just a weapon only when my father's
telling stories assistance would be
appreciated what are you making this
Tucker jungles dad never trust the
scientist don't break you here know
something act are monsters
werewolf vampire are you searching for a
way to return to the world once perhaps
but now I am at peace
what power binds you to this world
a magical catastrophe that told my
spirit from my body you blame yourself
for the Dragons reign of terror but it
is not your fault your work there you
don't know about my face
then you've seen as much as I teeth are
you laughs poor you come back this is
hot trust that lips I cannot see with my
own eyes I'd shake your hand but we're a
little busy now
Oh tie in the attempt
I hear dragons why do you ask
hi hot damn then I believe you heard
wrong subjects she's no true dragon but
surely the seminar is one of your
enemies
let us hope that this time it works out
better again
time has greatly changed us both we are
all of us always changing ultimate is
charged this is done we should fight
together again there are still many
enemies roaming the world our purpose is
to show everyone that in the iris we are
all one people when I gazed into the
iris I found a great nothingness it
changed me you must have experienced the
same he's not what awesome how can you
trust the countess after she slew your
master did I say I trusted her a pause
in the battle an opportunity to recenter
our minds I am Center there are times
even I cannot stand by
I'm going to be well-paid long ways home
for either of us some believe that the
full moon is a good omen the Summoner
wheels dragon magic there are those who
would give their souls to serve those
beasts crazy nuts a soldier an alchemist
an archer and unpalatable group we have
assemble here just as it has always been
you attract strange companions
if we survive the night this should be
our last battery no I cannot rest until
we have justice
the Reaper is a fearsome foe he may
still get the better of us I will get us
home safe as I always do why fight for
this Lord you have never cared much for
the nobility it is true but today we
share a common foe the Reaper
finish this fight old friend let us hope
we have the strength to see it through
what treason brings you to travel so far
from home I was banished from my home
for taking my brother's life I can never
return you say you do silence the good
dr. Duncan Stein would profess the same
science is a tool and a method the hand
that wields it decides its course I once
met a man who could summon a dragon as
you do impossible
only my clan possesses the skill my
brother could but he is dead what
difference is there between the witch's
magic and your alchemy alchemy is a
science her magic is something darker
I sense that you and the soldier have
history together indeed and much of it
unhappy I can tell you and the soldier
have some history together this is not
the office battle together and not the
lost unless he does something foolish
not sure how I feel about all this
alchemy nonsense
seems like hocus-pocus to me I could
leave you to die if you prefer do you
think that was the last of them
something tells me the worst is yet to
come
you do not trust my alchemy do you all
due respect witchcraft and magic potions
are no match for a good six shooter do
you think the doors would hold the doors
are not what I am concerned about
sort of monster do you think Arriba is
the worst kind there is a wicked man
drives a man to such madness to be
tested
to fail
surely dr. jeonghan Stein must be
running out of his machines he strikes
me as a man who had too many free hours
to invest in his pursuits my people
would call you a ronin a masterless
samurai Ronin I like the sound of their
what's home lag for you Archer a village
high atop the hill there are cherry
blossoms in the spring I miss it dearly
you're not bad with a bow but don't you
think it's a little old fashioned
perhaps there's still a future for
anachronisms you think this lords good
for the money
castle looks like it's seen better days
if he breaks his world he has made some
powerful enemies hey Archer what say you
pass that flask around so we can all
have a drink his is thirsty work
we drink when the job is done getting
tired gunslinger not a chance
doesn't seem to be any end to the
monsters
let them come I could always use the
practice you seem awful familiar you
sure we haven't met before maybe in
another life
what was that thing I'm trying to put it
out of my mind
everyone's still alive that seems so
that or the after laughs a big
disappointment you asked me you pump
something fool these chemicals
electricity and whatnot as not a man
it's a monster
maybe so or maybe they're not as
different as you think you don't seem
like someone who'd put his faith in
alchemy you have to believe in something
may as well be the thing that keeps you
alive so where are you from back home I
don't stay in one place for too long
came from a town called Bloomington
Indiana didn't expect to find another
American so far from home do you fight
in the war there's a man like me
fighting in every war